jbi.bike 2018-10-10

# JBI - Privacy Policy

Guaranteed Security Policy

We at J&B Importers, Inc. guarantee that your credit card and personal information are 100% safe and secure through the use of 128-bit SSL encryption technology. In addition to your information being secure, all data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.  

Privacy

Here at J&B Importers, Inc. your privacy is of utmost importance to us. Therefore, we will not sell, rent, share or loan your personal information to any unrelated third parties. We keep your personal information private and secure. When you make a purchase from our site, you provide your name, email address, address, phone number, and a password. We use this information to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience. Our secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption techniques and firewall technology. To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials and new additions to the J&B Importers, Inc. site. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us. When entering any of our contests or prize drawings, you provide your name, email address and mailing address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contests or drawing you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the J&B Importers, Inc. site. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received. We use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time.  

Privacy on Other Web Sites

Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. J&B Importers, Inc. is not responsible for the actions of third parties.  

Cookies

Cookies are small bits of information stored on your computer that keep track of items in your shopping cart. They personalize your visit throughout the site and let us know if you have visited J&B Importers, Inc. before. It is possible to navigate J&B Importers, Inc. without cookies, however, by not accepting cookies you may increase the time it takes you to navigate through our site. You may choose not to accept cookies by selecting that option in your web browser.
